Divya Dewan

M: +44 (0)7478-128250 E: dd558@jbs.cam.ac.uk LI: www.linkedin.com/in/divyadewan1 Visa: No Sponsorship Required

Professional with over 6.5 years of experience in digital transformation (DX) strategy, digital marketing, business development, enterprise solutioning & strategy consulting serving C-level executives at Fortune 500 enterprises spanning EMEA, APAC & the Americas. Proven record of consistently exceeding performance targets in fast-paced & disruptive environments, receiving two accelerated promotions over 3 years.

Education

	14 2022 4 2022
Professional experience	
Bachelor of Commerce (Honours); First Class Honours (83%; Top 3%)	
Hindu College, University of Delhi, India	Jun 2012 - Jun 2015
Associate Certified Coach (ACC) (Completed over 450+ coaching hours since 2018)	
International Coaching Federation	Dec 2021 - Onwards
Master of Business Administration (Digital Transformation Specialization); GMAT 720; Forté Fellow	
Judge Business School, University of Cambridge, UK	Sep 2021 - Sep 2022

Samsung Electronics, United Kingdom

Mar 2022 – Apr 2022

MBA Consultant (Digital Strategy)

- Partnered with Marketing Head to design omni-channel digital launch strategy for new Galaxy Book for GenZ segment across UK & I
- Conducted focus groups and leveraged digital analytics (Google Analytics, SFMC) to curate GenZ-driven buyer personas. Developed custom digital strategies & execution roadmaps for each persona to be rolled out in June 2022

Veris, Gurugram, India Jun 2018 – Jul 2021

High-growth SaaS Technology Startup (India's leading workplace automation platform)

Head, Strategic Marketing (Executive team member)

- Created US\$ 15m YoY lead pipeline (highest no. of leads to date) by directing 7-member team through digital GTM of new hybrid workplace platform across UK, US, & India enabling 1700+ offices to adapt to post-pandemic future of work
- Drove unique website visitors by 1.5x YoY & attained 120% of YoY lead growth target by segmenting key buyer personas & building personalized digital content strategies across purchase cycle
- Generated 40% cost savings in digital transformation audits by building fully automated and dynamic digital assessment framework rolled out across 250+ prospective client organizations over 18 months

Head, Enterprise Strategy & Sales

- Owned digital assessment, benchmarking, solution-design & commercial negotiation, winning 5-year contract for Pfizer, Veris' largest pan-global deal (US\$ 6m/yr.). Led 8-member cross-functional team with product managers & solution-architects
- Devised DX strategy, developed execution roadmaps & closed deals for 32+ F500 enterprise clients (67% of company revenues) by partnering with CHRO's, CIO's & IT Heads and designing customised digital solutions (L'Oreal, GAP, Barclays, etc)
- Enhanced productivity of 45-member salesforce from by 45% & win rate by 67% YoY by launching digital-advisory focussed training program leveraging micro-learning, simulation training & gamified testing

Manager, Strategy & Sales

- Managed, negotiated & closed accounts representing 45% of company revenues by winning contracts for 17+ F500 enterprises over 12 months. Achieved 154% of personal sales target & received early promotion to regional sales head (ZS Associates, RBS, JLL etc)
- Amplified reseller portfolio performance by 65% YoY, generating additional revenue of US\$ 12m. Led quarterly quota-setting workshops, monthly pipeline reviews & product-training bootcamps for 650-strong reseller network, globally

Hemera Global, Gurugram, India *Financial trading & consulting firm*

Apr 2017 – May 2018

Project Manager

- Crafted retail pricing strategy for \$200m consumer goods brand using 'value-pricing' approach. Managed 5-member cross-functional team in competitor benchmarking, trend analysis & focus groups across EMEA & APAC markets
- Increased 20% top-line for leading pharma company by designing optimal product-mix growth strategy focussed on 3 therapy areas

NirSan Connect, Gurugram, India

Jun 2015 - Mar 2017

Strategy consulting firm founded by ex-McKinsey partners

Business Analyst

- Devised 5-year revenue growth strategy for India's second largest pharma company to increase top-line growth by 2x. Facilitated goal setting & strategy workshops for 75+ mid & senior executives across India business unit (65% of company revenues)
- Increased marketing ROI by 50% for leading pharma company through strategic incentive & skill alignment of regional salesforce

Additional information

Leadership	Chair, Wo+Men Leadership Club, CJBS (155 members); Chair, Communication Club, CJBS; Chair, Oxbridge India Business Network (120+ members); Leader, Women in Tech India, Lean In.org
Awards/Honors	Forté Fellowship Scholarship Recipient (3 of 221 students) (2021); CJBS Bursary Award Winner (2021); Innovator of the Year at Veris (2020); Excellence at Work Awardee at NirSan (2017)
Social Influence	Active creator on LinkedIn (17000+ followers). Published work on DEI, implicit bias, personal growth and leadership innovation garnering over 2 million views from executives, globally (2020-Present)